Guide to the Theatre and Dance Department records, 1937-2011 RG0084
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Administrative files of Maida Withers, Professor of Dance, 1961-1993; 1967-1980; Series 12; Withers, Maida; 6 Linear Feet 4 record cartons
  - Dance Companies, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Dance Artists and Companies, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Acme Dance Company and James Cunningham, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Daniel McCusker, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Natalie Richman, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Ririe-Woodbury Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Don Redlich Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Rod Rogers, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Alvin Ailey Dance Theatre, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Airwaves, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - David Appel/Kinesonics, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Asian-American Dance Theatre, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Craig Babcock--Mime, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Barnes, Sue, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Ballet Folk of Moscow, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Les Ballet Jazz, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Les Ballet Trackadero de Monte Carlo, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Bat-Dor Dance Company of Israel, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Battery Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Tandy Beal and Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Margaret Beales, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Jill Becker and Dancers, Inc., undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - The Beverly Brown Dance Ensemble, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Beverly Brown--Special workshops, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Bowden, Sally, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Brown, Trisha, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Cal Arts California Institute of the Arts, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Deborah Earr Theatre Dance Ensemble, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Maria Carrico, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - John Randolph Carter, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Pat Catterson, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Colville, Priscilla, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Cohen, Ze'eva, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Conway, Carol, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Cohan Suzeau, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Ellen Cornfeild, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Cowles, Sage, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Pat Catterman, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Marilyn Wood and the Celebration Group, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Deborah Chassler, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - James Cunningham, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Dance Alliance, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Dance Alliance (England) Mary Folkerson, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Dance Gallery, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Duncan, Cathy, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Eliot Feld Ballet, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Laura Dean and Dancers, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Douglass Dunn, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Jeff Duncan, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Bill Evans Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Bill Evans, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Estampa Flamenca, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Louis Falco Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Viola Farber Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Lotte Gosler's Pantomime Circus, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Ara Fitzgerald, Kathy Kramer, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Simone Forti, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - John Gamble, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Annabelle Gamson, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Mimi Garrad Dance Theatre, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Diane Germaine, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Aydah Gorer, undated; Series 12 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - The Greenhouse Dance Ensemble, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Group Motion, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Marina Grut, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Calk Hook Dance Theatre, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Murray Louis Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Erick Hawkins Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Merce Cunningham, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Douglas Hamby Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Deborah Hay Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Harry--Dance and other works by Senta Driver, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Calk Hook, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Joe Jeff and the Wonder Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Pauline Koner Dance Consort, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Cheryl Banks, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Margaret Jonkins, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Cliff Kevter Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Laban, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Rachel Lampert and Dancers, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Pearl Lang and Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Lewitzky, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Jose Limon Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Margaret Jenkins Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Margalit and Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Victoria Marks, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Sophie Maslow Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Matteo Antho American Dance Theatre, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Barbara Mettler Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Metro Theatre Circus, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Mime Musica, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Minnesota Dance Theatre, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Modern Dance Ensemble, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Nagrin Dance Foundation, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Roger Neece, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Phoebe Neville, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Nancy Meehan Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Nikolais, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Rosalind Neman and Dancers, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Gale Ormiston Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Guest Artists, 1982; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Marleen Pennison, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - People/Dorothy Vislocky Dance Theatre, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Philobolus, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Eleo Pomare Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Kathryn Posin Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Buffy Price, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Clifford Shulman Dance Repertory, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Mitchell Rose, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Anne and Michael Sahl, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Mary Averet Seelye, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Jim Self, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Sheldon Soffer Management Inc., undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Snow, Faye, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Beth Soll and Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Nancy Spannier Dance Theatre, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Harry Streep III, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Jan Van Dyke and Dancers, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Le Corps Graphique, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Wykell, Luise, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Wendy Woodson, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Wendy Woodson, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - The Vakims, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Zero Moving Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Sahomi Tachibana--Japanese Dances, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Theatre Dance Collection, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Erika Thimey, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Tornay Management Inc., undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Three's Company--Jean Issacs, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Trinity Association, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Joyce Trisler Dance Company, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Eno Washington (West African), undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Publicity Brochures, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Dance Programs, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - NG Programs, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Photographs, Clippings, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - The Killing of Sister George, undated; Series 12 (Box 4, Folder 74)
- University Players, 1936-1964; 1947-1951; Series 13; 0.5 Linear Feet 1 document box
  This series contains photographs, scripts, and programs from University Players productions. The bulk of the series is photographs, and the material dates from 1936 to 1964, with the majority of material dating between 1947 and 1951.
  - Thompson, Julian - The Warrior Husband - Schedule and Annotated Script, 1950; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - GWU Drama - Correspondence regarding finances, 1948-1950; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Rip Van Winkle - Annotated Script, 1951; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Local Discussion Activities in Ohio, William E. Utterback, 1948; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Agamemnon - Photographs, 1948; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Programs and Script, circa 1947 to 1951; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Blithe Spirit - Photographs, circa 1946 to 1947; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Cinderella - Photographs, 1964; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dark of the Moon - Photographs, 1948; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - The Fan - Photographs, 1947; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - The Great Campaign - Photographs, 1948; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Heaven Can Wait - Photographs, circa 1947-1950; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Inspector General - Photographs, 1949; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - King Lear - Photographs, circa 1950; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Night Must Fall - Photographs, circa 1947-1949; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Of Thee I Sing - Photographs, 1946; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Puss in Boots - Photographs, circa 1946-1950; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - See Naples and Die - Photographs, 1936; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Somersault in the Sea - Photographs, 1949; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Twelfth Night - Photographs, circa 1945-1955; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - The Yellow Jacket - Photographs, 1949; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Tableaus based on the lives of Abraham Lincoln and Walter Reed - Photographs, circa 1945-1955; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Tableau showing Woodrom Wilson at the peace conference at Paris, following World War I - Photographs, circa 1945-1955; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Unidentified Play - Photographs, circa 1945-1950; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Unidentified Play - Photographs, circa 1945-1950; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Unidentified Play - Photographs, circa 1945-1950; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Unidentified Play - Photographs, circa 1945-1950; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Unidentified Play - Photographs, circa 1945-1950; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Unidentified Play - Photographs, circa 1945-1950; Series 13 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Promotions Office, 1956-2001; Series 14
  Arranged in the order of the original boxes by the donor.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Transferred by Theatre and Dance Promotions Office, December 1, 2011 (2011.080)
  This series contains photographs, slides, programs, and newspaper articles for theater and dance events. The materials date from 1956-2001.
  - Mainstage Season, 1974-1975; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    General
    Originally identified as folder 2
  - Mainstage Season, 1975-1976; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Originally identified as folder 3
  - Mainstage Season, 1980-1981; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    Originally identified as folder 11
  - Mainstage Season, 1971-1972; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Originally identified as folder 4
  - Mainstage Season, 1970-1971; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Originally identified as folder 5
  - Mainstage Season, 1977-1978; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Originally identified as folder 6
  - Mainstage Season, 1979-1980; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Originally identified as folder 7
  - Mainstage Season, 1973-1974; Series 14 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Originally identified as folder 8
  - Mainstage Season A Streetcar Named Desire, 1976 February 19-28; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Originally identified as folder 9
  - Mainstage Season, 1976-1977; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Originally identified as folder 10
  - Mainstage Season, 1980-1981; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Pliskin, Nancy, undated; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    Originally identified as folder 12
  - Letters Home, undated; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    Originally identified as folder 13
  - Mainstage Season, 1981-1982; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    Originally identified as folder 14
  - Arms and the Man, 1981-1982; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    Originally identified as folder 15
  - Mainstage Season, 1985-1986; Series 14 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Originally identified as folder 16
  - Mainstage Season, 1982-1983; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    Originally identified as folder 17
  - Mainstage Season, 1978-1979; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    Originally identified as folder 18
  - Mainstage Season The Glass Menagerie, 1978 October 9-14; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    Originally identified as folder 19
  - Mainstage Season, 1972-1973; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    Originally identified as folder 20
  - House of Blue Leave, 1988 April 14-16; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    Originally identified as folder 21
  - Paris When It Sizzled, 1998 April 16-19; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    Originally identified as folder 22
  - House of Yes, 1998 October 8-11; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    Originally identified as folder 23
  - Mainstage Season, 1968-1969; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    Originally identified as folder 24
  - Mainstage Season, 1969-1970; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    Originally identified as folder 25
  - The Hollow, 1999 February 25-28; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    Originally identified as folder 26
  - The Seagull, 1998 November 5-7; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    Originally identified as folder 27
  - Matchmaker, 1982-1983; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    Originally identified as folder 28
  - Midsummer Night's Dream, 1982-1983; Series 14 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    Originally identified as folder 29
  - Arcadia, 1998 February 26 - March 1; Series 14 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    Originally identified as folder 30
  - Professor Nathan Garner, 2006; Series 14 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Originally identified as folder 31
  - Mousetrap, 1982-1983; Series 14 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Originally identified as folder 32
  - Jacques Brel, 1983; Series 14 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Originally identified as folder 33
  - Richard II, 1976-1977; Series 14 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Originally identified as folder 34
  - Electra, 1981-1982; Series 14 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Originally identified as folder 35
  - Threepenny Opera photos, 1980-1981; Series 14 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Originally identified as folder 36
  - non-mainstage, undated; Series 14 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Originally identified as folder 37
  - Mainstage Season, 1984-1985; Series 14 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Originally identified as folder 38
  - Spring Dance Concert, 1988; Series 14 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Originally identified as folder 39
  - End Of The World, undated; Series 14 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Originally identified as folder 40
  - Cave Dwellers, 1985; Series 14 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Originally identified as folder 41
  - Another Part of the Forest, undated; Series 14 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    Originally identified as folder 42
  - Dracula photos, Summer and Smoke, Candide, Glass Managerie, 12th Night, Servant of 2 Masters, School for Wives, Richard II, GoodWoman, undated; Series 14 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    Originally identified as folder 43
  - Loose programs and photographs, undated; Series 14 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    These items were found in the bottom of the box.
  - Hay Fever, Lion of Winter, As you Like It, The lower slides of photos [1/2], 1975-1980; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Originally identified as folder 44
  - Hay Fever, Lion of Winter, As you Like It, The lower slides of photos [2/2], 1975-1980; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Slides of performances [1/3] Assyra, Ah! Wilderness, slides of photographs, undated; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    Originally identified as folder 1
  - Slides of performances [2/3] Assyra, Ah! Wilderness, slides of photographs, undated; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Slides of performances [3/3] Assyra, Ah! Wilderness, slides of photographs, undated; Series 14 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 2000-2001; Series 14 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1999-2000; Series 14 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1998-1999; Series 14 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1997-1998; Series 14 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1996-1997; Series 14 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1995-1996; Series 14 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1994-1995; Series 14 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1993-1994; Series 14 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1992-1993; Series 14 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1991-1992; Series 14 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1990-1991; Series 14 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1989-1990; Series 14 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1988-1989; Series 14 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1987-1988; Series 14 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1986-1987; Series 14 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1985-1986; Series 14 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1984-1985; Series 14 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1981-1982; Series 14 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1983-1984; Series 14 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1982-1983; Series 14 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1980-1981; Series 14 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1979-1980; Series 14 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1978-1979; Series 14 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1977-1978; Series 14 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1972-1973; Series 14 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1976-1977; Series 14 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Originally identified as folder 25 (as the previous one)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1975-1976; Series 14 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1973-1974; Series 14 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Originally identified as folder 26 (as the previous one)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1974-1975; Series 14 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1971-1972; Series 14 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1970-1971; Series 14 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1969-1970; Series 14 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1968-1969; Series 14 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1966-1967; Series 14 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1964-1965; Series 14 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1965-1966; Series 14 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1956-1957; Series 14 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1983-1993; series 14; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 bankers box Box 9 barcode: 32882019657405 (Box 9)
  - Mainstage Season programs, 1993-2005; series 14; 1.25 Linear Feet 1 bankers box barcode: 32882019657397 (Box 10)
- Productions, 1990-2011; Series 15; 0.5 Linear Feet
  Materials in this series are related to productions put on by the Theatre and Dance Department. Material dates from 1990-2011.
  Material maintains original order.
  - GW Theater Department of Theater and Dance, 1993-1997; Series 15 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Bokamoso Youth Project, 2006-2011; Series 15 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Strangers in a Strange Land, 1992; Series 15 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Croak the Last Frog, 1996; Series 15 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Croak the Last Frog, 1990-1996; Series 15 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Script-Croak of the Last Frog, Undated; Series 15 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - GW Three Roses Project, 2000; Series 15 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Dance Video Recordings, 2017-2019; Series 16
  The videos in this series document dance performances at GWU. Typically there are multiple videos for each performance that include a wide camera shot on one night; diagonal close up shot on another night, and a talk to the audience.
  The digital videos can be viewed in Box: https://gwu.box.com/s/h38kndq05zb5f5ud61puzsxvhvpmeeob